TUC General Committee Minutes and Papers on Microfilm 6113 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
TUC General Committee Minutes and Papers on Microfilm
1922- 1953
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Trades Union Congress (TUC)
6113 mf
2.78 cubic feet
25 microfilm reels
Microfilm.
9278423
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Biographical / Historical
The Trades Union Congress (TUC) is a national trade union centre, a federation of trade unions in England and Wales, representing the majority of trade unions. There are fifty-eight affiliated unions with a total of about 6.2 million members, around half of whom are represented by Unite or UNISON.
The TUC's decision-making body is the Annual Congress, which takes place in September. Between congresses decisions are made by the General Council, which meets every two months. An Executive Committee is elected by the Council from its members. [wikipedia]
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6112 mf: TUC Periodicals and Serials on Microfilm 6114 mf: TUC Archives on The Mining Crisis and The Genral Strike on Microfilm 6115 fiche: TUC Archives on Microfiche
Labor unions -- Great Britain -- History; Trades Union Congress.
9278423
- Co-ordination Committee File 1, Disputes Committee Vols. 1-4 (Reel 1)
  - Co-Ordination Committee: Box 15, File 1, 1920-1922; 1 (Reel 1)
    Scope and Contents
    October 1920 - February 1922
  - Disputes Committee: Volume 1, 1923-1924; 2 (Reel 1)
    15 October 1923-31 August 1924
  - Disputes Committee: Volume 2, 1924-1925; 3 (Reel 1)
    29 September 1924 - 24 August 1925
  - Disputes Committee: Volume 3, 1925-1926; 4 (Reel 1)
    20 October 1925 - 11 August 1926
  - Disputes Committee: Volume 4, 1926-1930; 5 (Reel 1)
    4 November 1926 - 25 March 1930
- Disputes Committee Vols. 5-8 (Reel 2)
  - Disputes Committee: Volume 5, 1930-1936; 1 (Reel 2)
    19 November 1930 - 15 July 1936
  - Disputes Committee: Volume 2, 1936-1940; 2 (Reel 2)
    13 October 1936 - 7 May 1940
  - Disputes Committee: Volume 7, 1940-1948; 3 (Reel 2)
    2 August 1940 - 29 July 1948
  - Disputes Committee: Volume 8, 1948-1953; 4 (Reel 2)
    27 October 1948 - 2 November 1953
- Economic Committee Files 1-4 (Reel 3)
  - Economic Committee: Box 1254, File 1, 1929-1937; 1 (Reel 3)
    19 April 1929 - 30 July 1937
  - Economic Committee: Box 1254, File 2, 1937-1939; 2 (Reel 3)
    13 October 1937 - 19 July 1939
  - Economic Committee: Box 1254, File 3, 1940-1944; 3 (Reel 3)
    14 November 1940 - 29 September 1944
  - Economic Committee: Box 1254, File 4, 4 (Reel 3)
    Missing
- Economic Committee Files 5-8 (Reel 4)
  - Economic Committee: Box 1255, File 5, 1 (Reel 4)
  - Economic Committee: Box 1255, File 6, 1947-1949; 2 (Reel 4)
    8 October 1947 - 25 Jul 1949
  - Economic Committee: Box 1255, File 7, 1949-1950; 3 (Reel 4)
    11 November 1949 - 9 August 1950
  - Economic Committee: Box 1255, File 8, 1950-1951; 4 (Reel 4)
    11 October 1950 - 8 August 1951
- Economic Committee Files 9-10 (Reel 5)
  - Economic Committee: Box 1256, File 9, 1951-1952; 1 (Reel 5)
    14 November 1951 - 18 June 1952
  - Economic Committee: Box 1256, File 10, 1952-1953; 2 (Reel 5)
    8 October 1952 - 10 June 1953
- Education Committee Files 1-4 (Reel 6)
  - Education Committee: Box 1847, File 1, 1922-1925; 1 (Reel 6)
    23 February 1922 - 30 November1925
  - Education Committee: Box 1847, File 2, 1926-1933; 2 (Reel 6)
    29 September 1926 - 21 August 1933
  - Education Committee: Box 1847, File 3, 1933-1938; 3 (Reel 6)
    16 November 1933 - 30 August 1938
  - Education Committee: Box 1847, File 4, 1938-1940; 4 (Reel 6)
    3 October 1938 - 16 July 1940
- Education Committee Files 5-9 (Reel 7)
  - Education Committee: Box 1848, File 5, 1940-1943; 1 (Reel 7)
    17 December 1940 - 11 August 1943
  - Education Committee: Box 1848, File 6, 1943-1945; 2 (Reel 7)
    20 October 1943 - 19 June 1945
  - Education Committee: Box 1848, File 7, 1945-1947; 3 (Reel 7)
    24 October 1945 - 12 August 1937
  - Education Committee: Box 1848, File 8, 1947-1948; 4 (Reel 7)
    14 September 1947 - 19 August 1948
  - Education Committee: Box 1848, File 9, 1948-1949; 5 (Reel 7)
    12 October 1948 - 12 July 1949
- Education Committee Files 10-11 (Reel 8)
  - Education Committee: Box 1849, File 10, 1948-1951; 1 (Reel 8)
    11 October 1949 - 11 August 1951
  - Education Committee: Box 1849, File 11, 1949-1953; 2 (Reel 8)
    9 October 1949 - 14 Jul 1953
- Finance and General Purposes Committee Vols. 1-6 (Reel 9)
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 1, 1923-1925; 1 (Reel 9)
    24 September 1923 - 14 August 1925
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 2, 1925-1927; 2 (Reel 9)
    14 November 1925 - 23 August 1927
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 3, 1927-1929; 3 (Reel 9)
    23 September 1927 - 23 September 1929
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 4, 1929-1930; 4 (Reel 9)
    16 October 1929 - 22 August 1930
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 5, 1930-1932; 5 (Reel 9)
    13 October 1930 - 22 August 1932
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 6, 1932-1934; 6 (Reel 9)
    24 October 1932 - 24 September 1934
- Finance and General Purposes Committee Vols. 7-9 (Reel 10)
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 7, 1934-1936; 1 (Reel 10)
    22 October 1934 - 20 July 1936
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 8, 1936-1938; 2 (Reel 10)
    26 October 1936 - 6 July 1938
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 9, 1938-1939; 3 (Reel 10)
    24 October 1938 -25 September 1939
- Finance and General Purposes Committee Vols.10-12 (Reel 11)
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 10, 1938-1941; 1 (Reel 11)
    23 October 1939 - 28 August 1941
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 11, 2 (Reel 11)
    27 October 1941 - 23 August 1943
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 12, 1943-1945; 3 (Reel 11)
    28 September 1943 - 22 October 1945
- Finance and General Purposes Committee Vols. 13-17 (Reel 12)
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 13, 1945-1946; 1 (Reel 12)
    26 November 1945 - 18 September 1946
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 14, 1946-1948; 2 (Reel 12)
    25 November 1946 - 30 August 1948
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 15, 1948-1950; 3 (Reel 12)
    22 October 1948 - 3 August 1950
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 16, 1950; 4 (Reel 12)
    October 1950 - Jul 1950
  - Finance and General Purpose Committee: Volume 17, 1952-1953; 5 (Reel 12)
    20 October 1952 - 21 December 1953
- Colonial Advisory Committee Files 1-2, Part 2 International Committee Files 1-4 (Reel 13)
  - Colonial Advisory Committee: Box 1447, File 1, 1937-1952; 1 (Reel 13)
    22 December 1937 - 11 July 1952
  - Colonial Advisory Committee: Box 1447, File 2, 1942-1953; 2 (Reel 13)
    10 November 1942 - 29 July 1953
  - International Committee: Box 1853, File 1, 1923-1928; 3 (Reel 13)
    10 December 1923 - 29 June 1928
  - International Committee: Box 1853, File 2, 1928-1930; 4 (Reel 13)
    19 September 1928 - 19 August 1930
  - International Committee: Box 1853, File 3, 1930-1934; 5 (Reel 13)
    21 October 1930 - 18 September 1934
  - International Committee: Box 1853, File 4, 1934-1937; 6 (Reel 13)
    20 November 1934 - 17 April 1937
- Part 2 International Committee Files 5-7 (Reel 14)
  - International Committee: Box 1854, File 5, 1937-1942; 1 (Reel 14)
    26 October 1937 - 7 September 1942
  - International Committee: Box 1854, File 6, 1942-1945; 2 (Reel 14)
    27 October 1942 - 21 August 1945
  - International Committee: Box 1854, File 7, 1945-1947; 3 (Reel 14)
    27 November 1945 - 22 July 1947
- Part 2 International Committee Files 8-10 (Reel 15)
  - International Committee: Box 1854, File 8, 1947-1949; 1 (Reel 15)
    14 October 1947 - July 1949
  - International Committee: Box 1855, File 9, 1949-1951; 2 (Reel 15)
    25 October 1949 - 29 May 1951
  - International Committee: Box 1855, File 10, 1951-1953; 3 (Reel 15)
    30 October 1951 - 21 July 1953
- Part 2 Non-Manual Workers Advisory Committee Files 1-3 (Reel 16)
  - Non-Manual Workers Advisory Committee: Box 1825, File 1, 1931-1943; 1 (Reel 16)
    16 January 1931 - 27 July 1943
  - Non-Manual Workers Advisory Committee: Box 1825, File 2, 1943-1950; 2 (Reel 16)
    12 October 1943 - 1 August 1950
  - Non-Manual Workers Advisory Committee: Box 1825, File 3, 1950-1953; 3 (Reel 16)
    19 October 1950 - 14 July 195
- Part 2 Organization Committee Files 1-5 (Reel 17)
  - Organisation Committee: Box 1236, File 1, 1924-1926; 1 (Reel 17)
    16 December 1924 - 20 July 1926
  - Organisation Committee: Box 1236, File 2, 1926-1936; 2 (Reel 17)
    7 December 1926 - 13 August 1936
  - Organisation Committee: Box 1236, File 3, 1936-1943; 3 (Reel 17)
    29 October 1936 - 12 July 1943
  - Organisation Committee: Box 1236, File 4, 1943-1949; 4 (Reel 17)
    18 November 1943 - 12 July 1949
  - Organisation Committee: Box 1236, File 5, 1949-1953; 5 (Reel 17)
    19 October 1949 - 30 June 1953
- Part 2 Social Insurance Advisory Committee Files 1-5 (Reel 18)
  - Social Insurance Advisory Committee: Box 1246, File 1, 1928-1930; 1 (Reel 18)
    April 1928 - 12 June 1930
  - Social Insurance Advisory Committee: Box 1246, File 2, 1930-1933; 2 (Reel 18)
    2 October 1930 - 17 August 1933
  - Social Insurance Advisory Committee: Box 1246, File 3, 1933-1936; 3 (Reel 18)
    21 September 1933 - 13 August 1936
  - Social Insurance Advisory Committee: Box 1246, File 4, 1936-1939; 4 (Reel 18)
    8 October 1936 - 9 January 1939
  - Social Insurance Advisory Committee: Box 1246, File 5, 1939-1947; 5 (Reel 18)
    12 October 1939 - 9 January 1947
- Part 2 Social Insurance and Industrial Welfare Committee Files 1-4 (Reel 19)
  - Social Insurance and Welfare Committee: Box 1247, File 1, 1947-1949; 1 (Reel 19)
    12 November 1947 - 21 July 1949
  - Social Insurance and Welfare Committee: Box 1247, File 2, 1949-1950; 2 (Reel 19)
    12 October 1949 - 12 July 1950
  - Social Insurance and Welfare Committee: Box 1247, File 3, 1950-1951; 3 (Reel 19)
    11 October 1950 - 11 July 1951
  - Social Insurance and Welfare Committee: Box 1247, File 4, 1951-1952; 4 (Reel 19)
    10 October 1951 - 12 August 1952
- Social Insurance and Industrial Welfare Committee Part 2, File 5 (Reel 20)
  - Social Insurance and Welfare Committee: Box 1248, File 5, 1952-1953; 1 (Reel 20)
    8 October 1952 - 12 August 1953
  - Joint Social Insurance and Workmen's Compensation and Factories Comimittee: Box 1248, File 1, 1941-1945; 2 (Reel 20)
    24 July 1941 - 2 August 1945
  - Joint Social Insurance and Workmen's Compensation and Factories Comimittee: Box 1248, File 2, 1945-1948; 3 (Reel 20)
    15 November 1945 - 13 October 1948
  - Scientific Advisory Council: Box 1842, File 1, 1939-1952; 4 (Reel 20)
    13 June 1939 - 31 January 1952
- Part 2 Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee Files 1-4 (Reel 21)
  - Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee: Box 1241, File 1, 1924-1927; 1 (Reel 21)
    7 May 1294 - 28 July 1927
  - Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee: Box 1241, File 2, 1927-1935; 2 (Reel 21)
    25 October 1927 - 16 July 1935
  - Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee: Box 1241, File 3, 1935-1940; 3 (Reel 21)
    15 October 1935 - 26 July 1940
  - Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee: Box 1241, File 4, 1940-1944; 4 (Reel 21)
    12 December 1940 - 6 October 1944
- Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee Part 2, Files 5-7, Trade Boards Advisory Council Files 1-2, Unemployment Joint Advisory Committee, File 1 (Reel 22)
  - Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee: Box 1242, File 5, 1944-1949; 1 (Reel 22)
    28 November 1944 - 22 August 1949
  - Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee: Box 1242, File 6, 1949-1952; 2 (Reel 22)
    17 October 1949 - 21 July 1952
  - Trades Council Joint Consultative Committee: Box 1242, File 7, 1952-1953; 3 (Reel 22)
    23 October 1952 - 23 July 1953
  - Trade Board Advisory Council: Box 1836, File 1, 1923-1938; 4 (Reel 22)
    December 1923 - Jul 1938
  - Trade Board Advisory Council: Box 1836, File 2, 1938-1953; 5 (Reel 22)
    1 November 1938 - 18 February 1953
  - Unemployment Joint Advisory Committee: Box 1, File 1, 1924-1926; 6 (Reel 22)
    9 May 1924 - 19 August 1926
- Women Workers Group File 1. Part 2 National Womens Advisory Committee, Files 2-7 (Reel 23)
  - Women Workers Group: Box 1238, File 1, 1922-1931; 1 (Reel 23)
    15 February 1922 - 8 January 1931
  - National Women's Advisory Committee: Box 1238, File 2, 1931-1934; 2 (Reel 23)
    18 March 1931 - 9 March 1934
  - National Women's Advisory Committee: Box 1238, File 3, 1934-1940; 3 (Reel 23)
    12 October 1934 - 12 September 1940
  - National Women's Advisory Committee: Box 1238, File 4, 1940-1944; 4 (Reel 23)
    14 November 1940 - 26 October 1944
  - National Women's Advisory Committee: Box 1238, File 5, 1944-1949; 5 (Reel 23)
    13 December 1944 - 6 July 1949
  - National Women's Advisory Committee: Box 1238, File 6, 1949-1951; 6 (Reel 23)
    5 October 1949 - 4 July 1951
  - National Women's Advisory Committee: Box 1238, File 7, 1951-1953; 7 (Reel 23)
    7 November 1951 - 1 July 1953
- Part 2 Joint Workmens Compensation Committee File 1. Joint Committee of the Workmens Compensation Bill, File 2 and Factories Committee Files 3-6 (Reel 24)
  - Joint Workmen's Compensation Committee: Box 1233, File 1, 1924-1943; 1 (Reel 24)
    3 April 1924 - 19 January 1943
  - Joint Committee of the Workmen's Compensation Bill: Box 1244, File 2, 1929-1943; 2 (Reel 24)
    28 November 1929 - 19 January 1943
  - Workmen's Compensation and Factories Committee: Box 1244, File 3, 1929-1934; 3 (Reel 24)
    29 November 1929 - 11 July 1934
  - Workmen's Compensation and Factories Committee: Box 1244, File 4, 1934-1936; 4 (Reel 24)
    20 September 1934 - 17 September 1936
  - Workmen's Compensation and Factories Committee: Box 1244, File 5, 1936-1939; 5 (Reel 24)
    24 September 1936 - 19 July 1939
  - Workmen's Compensation and Factories Committee: Box 1245, File 6, 1939-1942; 6 (Reel 24)
    11 October 1939 - 15 July 1942
- Workmens Compensation and Factories Committee, Part 2, Files 7-8. Trades Union Sub-Committee and Groups 1922-1926, Vols. 1-2 (Reel 25)
  - Workmen's Compensation and Factories Committee: Box 1245, File 7, 1942-1945; 1 (Reel 25)
    22 October 1942 - 23 August 1945
  - Workmen's Compensation and Factories Committee: Box 1245, File 8, 1945-1947; 2 (Reel 25)
    22 October 1945 - 8 September 1947
  - Trades Union Sub-Committee and Grooups: Volume 1, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 25)
    7 February 1922 - 7 May 1923
  - Trades Union Sub-Committee and Grooups: Volume 2, 1922-1926; 4 (Reel 25)
    13 April 1922 - 26 January 1926